Edward C. Blomeyer photographic collection, Inclusive: 1906-1923, Bulk: 1912-1920
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Texas., 1906-1920; 2
  - Central and South Texas, 2
    - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes, 1906-1920; 3
      San Antonio: The exterior of the Alamo, San Antonio, Texas. E.C. Blomeyer took this photograph in about 1906, prior to moving to this state in 1912. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4 ½-inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-754.2.tif.
      Austin: A scenic view of early Austin, Texas, with the Texas State Capitol in the distance. The digital image is from a scan of a 1 ¾ by 2 ¾-inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-800.09.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912.
      Gulf Coast: This photograph shows an early view of the the Galveston Causeway and the original railroad bridge across this span. On the back of the printed version of this photograph, Blomeyer made note of the telephone lines stretching alongside the structures. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-795.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912.
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Austin, TX: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-800.11.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:198)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Austin, TX: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-800.10.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:199)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Austin, TX: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-800.09.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:200)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Austin, TX: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-800.08.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:201)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Austin, TX: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-800.07.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:202)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Austin, TX: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-688.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:203)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Austin, TX: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-706.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:204)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Austin, TX., 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:205)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Austin, TX., 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:206)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Galveston/Gulf Coast: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-785.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:207)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Galveston Causeway: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-795.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:208)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Man in Boat-Galveston/Gulf Coast: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-759.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:209)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast-Crashing Waves, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:210)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Galveston: Hotel Galvez and Seawall: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-922.4.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:211)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Galveston: Hotel Galvez, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:212)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Galveston: Hotel Galvez, Man, and Seawall, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:213)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Galveston, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:214)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Galveston: Hotel Galvez: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-816.11.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:215)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast: Boats in Harbor, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:216)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast: Moonlight Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:217)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast: Moonlight Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:218)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast: Moonlight Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:219)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coasts: Crashing Waves, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:220)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast: Moonlight Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:221)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Freight Ships at Port, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:222)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast: Mary Blomeyer and Sons on Shoreline, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:223)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast: Mary Blomeyer and Sons on Shoreline, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:224)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Building Entrance with Palm Tree, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:225)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast Scene with Beach Homes, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:226)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Blomeyer Boys Looking at the Water from Beach, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:227)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast Scene with the Blomeyer’s at Beach, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:228)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast Scene with the Blomeyer’s at Beach, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:229)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast Scene with Boats, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:230)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast Scene with Amma, Edward and Earle Blomeyer at Beach, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:231)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast scene with Edward and Earle Blomeyer at Beach, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:232)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast Scene with Mary Blomeyer at Beach, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:233)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast Scene with People Eating Near Beach, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:234)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast Scene with Edward and Earle Playing on the Rocks, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:235)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes-Gulf Coast scene with Edward and Earle playing on the rocks, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:236)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Gulf Coast Scene with the Blomeyer’s and Group of People Sitting near Beach, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:237)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: New Braunfels: Waterfall/Spring, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:238)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: New Braunfel:, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:239)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: New Braunfels, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:240)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: New Braunfels, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:241)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Alamo: Digitized ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-395.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:242)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Alamo: Digitized ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-396.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:243)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Alamo: Digitized ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-397.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:244)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Alamo: Digitized ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-754.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:245)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Missions, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:246)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Alamo Plaza: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-781.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:247)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Mission Interior, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:248)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Missions, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:249)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Missions: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-923.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:250)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: South Pacific Depot: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-816.10.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:251)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Alamo Plaza: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-759.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:252)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Mission Interior, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:253)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Alamo Plaza: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-761.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:254)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Street Scenes: Houses and Palms, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:255)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: Railroad Depot, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:256)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: River Walk, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:257)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: San Antonio: River Walk, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:258)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:259)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar: Home, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:260)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:261)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-802.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:262)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:263)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:264)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:265)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:266)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:267)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:268)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:269)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:270)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:271)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: “A Texas Rainbow”, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:272)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Waxahachie: Street Scene: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-816.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:273)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Waxahachie: Street Scene: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-816.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:274)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Scenic: Texas Hill Country, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:275)
      - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes: Scenic: Texas Hill Country, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:276)
      - Cities: Austin and San Antonio, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Cities: Gulf Coast and Galveston, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Cities: Gulf Coast, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Cities: Gulf Coast, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Cities: New Braunfels and Hill Country, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Cities: Tyler: Lake Greenbriar, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Oil and Natural Gas Field, circa 1920; 4
      This group of photographs shows one of Texas' many booming oil and natural gas fields of the early 20th century. Its location is unknown.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-773.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-776.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-881.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-808.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-879.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-887.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-806.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-886.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-886.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-799.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-799.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: 3886-Blomeyer-799-2. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-806.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-756.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Pictured is an unidentified Texas town that was a location for oil and natural gas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-806.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:277)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-879.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:278)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-756.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:279)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-886.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:280)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-886.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:281)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-887.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:282)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-806.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:283)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-806.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:284)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-806.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:285)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-808.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:286)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-776.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:287)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-773.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:288)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-799.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:289)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:290)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:291)
      - Oil and Natural Gas Field, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Vacation, 1912-1920; 3
  Ranging from Arkansas to Canada, E.C. Blomeyer and family took many trips that they documented through taking photographs of their favorite scenes, activities, living spaces, and people they knew or met on their journeys.
  - Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920; 1
    This subseries shows pictures E.C. Blomeyer took while on vacation at Bella Vista, Benton County, Arkansas. Images are of lakes, wooded areas and trails, water falls, caves, cabins, and various people including family members.
    Unidentified vacationers at Bella Vista, Arkansas, pose with a well-traveled auto. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-vacat-948.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
    Bella Vista, Arkansas, was a popular vacation spot enjoyed by the Blomeyer family. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-vacat-948.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:1)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:2)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:3)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:4)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:5)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:6)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:7)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:8)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:9)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:10)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:11)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:12)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:13)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:14)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:15)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:16)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:17)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:18)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:19)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:20)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:21)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:22)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-948.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:23)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:24)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-948.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:25)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-948.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:26)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:27)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:28)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:29)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:30)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:31)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:32)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:33)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:34)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:35)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Vacation: Bella Vista, Arkansas, 1912-1920 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Colorado: Royal Gorge Route & Pikes Peak, 1912-1920; 2
    The printed photographs in this series show the observation tower at the top of Pikes Peak and the cog train rail track that leads to it. Also shown is Royal Gorge, Canon City, and the railroad route that travels through the mountain range.
    - George Washington Monument, Milwaukee, Wisconsin: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-950.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3:40)
    - (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:41)
    - Vacation: Colorado, 1912-1920 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Mount Pisgah, North Carolina, 1912-1920; 3
    This subseries includes images taken of the trails and views on Mount Pisgah, North Carolina. Most of the images are views taken of the surrounding Appalachian mountain ranges from the mountain top.
    - Vacation: Mount Pisgah, North Carolina, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:36)
    - Vacation: Mount Pisgah, North Carolina, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:37)
    - Vacation: Mount Pisgah, North Carolina, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:38)
    - Vacation: Mount Pisgah, North Carolina, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:39)
    - Vacation: Mount Pisgah, North Carolina, 1906-1920 (Folder 5)
    - Mount Pisgah, North Carolina, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Potomac Canal, George Washington's Tomb and Monument, 1912-1920; 4
    This subseries includes images of the exterior of George Washington's tomb in Mt. Vernon, Virginia, and a park service employee overseeing it. Another image shows the George Washington Monument in Milwaukee, Wisconsin. Scenic views of the Potomac Canal around Maryland and Virginia are included; E.C. Blomeyer is photographed standing on its banks.
    George Washington Monument in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, located on the Court of Honor. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ½ by 4 ½ -inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-vacat-950.3.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912.
    - George Washington Monument, Milwaukee, Wisconsin tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-950.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3:40)
    - Potomac Canal, George Washington's Tomb and Monument, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Potomac Canal and Area, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, 1912-1920; 5